DEVANSH SRIVASTAVA

Graphic Designer | UI/UX Designer

Portfolio

https://groovydesignstudio.github.io

Contact

E-mail

srivastava002dev@gmail.com

Phone

8077599341, 8445609245

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/devansh-srivastava-08

Address

Uttrakhand, 244713

Key Skills

Graphic Design

UI/UX Design

Visual Design

Web Design

Vector Illustration

Software

Figma

Adobe Xd

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Dimentions

Adobe Indesign

Canva

Creative years experienced of Graphic and UI/UX Designs adept in creating powerful visual designs using digital illustration, images and typography. committed to helping clients shape their brand identity through the use of compelling graphics. Accustomed to collaborating with other creative professionals to achieve project goals.

Work History

May 2021-August 2021

Fliqaindia

Graphic Designer & UI Designer

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed website layouts, templates and unique branded looks.
- Worked with Software and Type of design systems to develop and present prototypes for focus group evaluation.
- Applied creative expertise to present marketing concepts.
- Created broad range of work using various design techniques.
- Created designs and collaborated with technical team to complete projects.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Used photoshop to develop product mockups and prototype designs.

January 2021-March 2021

Helpholics

Graphic Designer

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed creative digital displays used in on-line advertising for local businesses.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Put together videos for social media, advertising and informational purposes.
- Capitalized on talents in field to support promotions with many designs.
- Completed key different design projects for clients.

July 2020-September 2020

Sportsthat

Graphic Designer

- Promoted company's events by designing marketing materials such as posters, digital invites and brochures.
- Prepared images to coincide with social and blog posts.
- Used Photoshop and Illustrator to create images and layouts for multiple projects.
- Capitalized on talents in field to support promotions with many designs.

DEVANSH SRIVASTAVA

Graphic Designer | UI/UX Designer

Interests

Football

Badminton

Athletics

Making designs

Language

Hindi

English

Spanish (Beginner)

November 2019-January 2020

Carpathy

Graphic Designer

- Worked closely with Carpathy to maintain optimum levels of communication to effectively and efficiently complete projects.
- Applied knowledge of production to create high-quality images.
- Developed creative design for marketing packages, including print materials, brochures, banners and signs.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to ensure projects were completed on time.

June 2019-August 2019

Talentedge

Graphic Designer

- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Developed Application UIs via emerging Front End Technologies
- Created maps, models and templates for diverse projects.
- · Created design work for digital campaigns.
- Prepared images to coincide with social and blog posts.
- Completed key design projects for company.

Education

August 2017-August 2020 **Bachelor of Design: Graphic Design**

Apeejay Stya University - Haryana

References: Available on request